[
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Andhra Pradesh",
    "answer":"Amaravati",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Arunachal Pradesh",
    "answer":"Itanagar",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Assam",
    "answer":"Dispur",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Bihar",
    "answer":"Patna",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Chhattisgarh",
    "answer":"Raipur",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Goa",
    "answer":"Panaji",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Gujarat",
    "answer":"Gandhinagar",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Haryana",
    "answer":"Chandigarh",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Himachal Pradesh",
    "answer":"Shimla",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Jharkhand",
    "answer":"Ranchi",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Karnataka",
    "answer":"Bengaluru",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Kerala",
    "answer":"Thiruvananthapuram",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Madhya Pradesh",
    "answer":"Bhopal",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Maharashtra",
    "answer":"Mumbai",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Manipur",
    "answer":"Imphal",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Meghalaya",
    "answer":"Shillong",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Mizoram",
    "answer":"Aizawl",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Nagaland",
    "answer":"Kohima",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Odisha",
    "answer":"Bhubaneswar",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Punjab",
    "answer":"Chandigarh",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Rajasthan",
    "answer":"Jaipur",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Sikkim",
    "answer":"Gangtok",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Tamil Nadu",
    "answer":"Chennai",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Telangana",
    "answer":"Hyderabad",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Tripura",
    "answer":"Agartala",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Uttar Pradesh",
    "answer":"Lucknow",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Uttarakhand",
    "answer":"Dehradun",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"West Bengal",
    "answer":"Kolkata",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Andaman and Nicobar Island",
    "answer":"Port Blair",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Chandigarh",
    "answer":"Chandigarh",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Dadra and Nagar Haveli and Daman and Diu",
    "answer":"Daman",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Delhi",
    "answer":"Delhi",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Ladakh",
    "answer":"NA",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Lakshadweep",
    "answer":"Kavaratti",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Jammu and Kashmir",
    "answer":"NA",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  },
  {
    "type":"mcq_random",
    "question":"Puducherry",
    "answer":"Pondicherry",
    "ansSet":"states_capitals"
  }
]